# **Cameron Ware**

Monrovia, CA| 376-7251 | cameronware@me.com

### **Professional Summary**

I am currently a professional swim coach looking for a career change into IT. Through my years of coaching I have learned leadership, and how to effectively communicate with people from all educational, socio-economic, and religious backgrounds. Personally, I have built gaming PC's for the last five years, am currently self-studying for the CompTIA A+, and am enrolled in a CCNA program at my local college.

#### **Education**

### Pasadena City College | Pasadena, CA

2019-Present

Computer Information Systems

## **Technical Knowledge**

- PC Hardware: Install, Configure, Troubleshoot
- Mobile Devices: Laptop repair and mobile phone connectivity/synchronization
- OS: Windows 10, Mac OS, iOS

### **Work History**

### Senior Development Coach | Rose Bowl Aquatics, Pasadena CA

2010 - Present

- Collaborated closely with a team of 18 coaches to lead a group of 500+ swimmers to become a top 24 swim team out of 6500+ in the United States.
- Managed a group of 100+ swimmers.
- · Developed multiple nationally ranked swimmers.
- Helped fundraise over \$120,000 for the USA Swimming Swim-A-Thon each year from 2014-2019.

### Host/Server | El Cholo Café, Pasadena CA

2012-2013

- Effectively resolved customer conflicts in a friendly and timely manner during high-volume operations.
- Ensured optimal customer experience through excellent communication skills, a positive attitude, and being empathetic to their needs.
- Familiarized guests with menu and daily specials, accurately recorded food and drink orders, and ran multi-course meals.
- Managed orders and financial transactions using digital POS system.

### Certifications

CompTIA A+ (in progress)